ohgizmo.com 2019-07-03

# Privacy Policy | OhGizmo!

OhGizmo is committed to respecting the privacy rights of its customers and other users of the OhGizmo Website (all capitalized terms not defined in this Notice have the same meanings as in OhGizmo’s Website Terms of Use). OhGizmo created this Privacy Policy to give You confidence as You visit and use the Website, and to demonstrate its commitment to fair information practices and to the protection of Your privacy.  
This Privacy Policy is only applicable to the Website, and not to any Third-Party Websites, which, as further explained below, may have data collection, storage and use practices and policies that differ materially from this Privacy Policy.  Nor is this Privacy Policy applicable to information provided to OhGizmo in connection with transactions occurring other than by means of the Website.

BY USING THE WEBSITE, YOU REPRESENT AND WARRANT THAT YOU HAVE READ AND UNDERSTOOD, AND AGREE TO THE TERMS OF, THIS PRIVACY POLICY.  IF YOU DO NOT UNDERSTAND OR DO NOT AGREE TO BE BOUND BY THIS PRIVACY POLICY, YOU MUST IMMEDIATELY LEAVE THE WEBSITE.

1\.  CHANGES  
EACH TIME YOU USE THE WEBSITE, THE THEN-CURRENT VERSION OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY WILL APPLY.  ALTHOUGH MOST CHANGES ARE LIKELY TO BE MINOR, OhGizmo RESERVES THE RIGHT TO CHANGE THIS PRIVACY POLICY AT ANY TIME, NOTICE OF ANY SUCH CHANGE TO BE GIVEN BY THE POSTING OF A REVISED VERSION OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY AND/OR A CHANGE NOTICE.  ACCORDINGLY, EACH TIME YOU USE THE WEBSITE, YOU SHOULD CHECK THE DATE OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY (WHICH APPEARS AT THE END) AND, IF LATER THAN YOUR LAST VISIT TO THE WEBSITE, REVIEW THIS PRIVACY POLICY FOR CHANGES.  IF YOU FIND ANY CHANGE UNACCEPTABLE, YOU MUST IMMEDIATELY LEAVE AND CEASE TO USE THE WEBSITE.  Unless OhGizmo obtains Your express consent, any revised Privacy Policy will apply only to information collected by OhGizmo after such revised Privacy Policy takes effect, and not to information collected under any earlier Privacy Policies.

2\. ELIGIBILITY TO USE WEBSITE?The Website is hosted and operated from within the United States.  As stated in the Terms of Use, use of the Website is restricted to United States residents 18 years of age or older.  OhGizmo does not intend to, and will not knowingly, collect information from or about individuals located outside the United States or individuals younger than 18 years of age.

3\. INFORMATION COLLECTION PRACTICES?(a) Traffic Data.  Like most website operators, OhGizmo gathers information of the sort that browsers automatically make available, including:  (i) IP addresses (ii) domain servers (iii) types of computers accessing the Website and (iv) types of Web browsers accessing the Website (collectively “Traffic Data”).  Traffic Data is anonymous information that does not personally identify You.  
(b) Cookies.  A “Cookie” is a string of information that a website stores on a user&amprsquos computer, and that the user’s browser provides to the website each time the user submits a query to the website.  The purpose of a Cookie is to identify the user as a unique user of the Website.  OhGizmo may use Cookies to customize Your experience on the Website to Your presumed interests, to ensure that You do not see the same advertisements or informational messages repeatedly, and to store Your user name and password so You do not have to re-enter them each time You visit the Website.  For additional information on OhGizmo’s use of Cookies, see the section concerning Information Use and Disclosure Practices/Traffic Data and Information Gathered Using Cookies, below.  
IF YOU DO NOT WISH TO HAVE COOKIES PLACED ON YOUR COMPUTER, YOU SHOULD SET YOUR BROWSER TO REFUSE COOKIES BEFORE ACCESSING THE WEBSITE, WITH THE UNDERSTANDING THAT CERTAIN FEATURES OF THE WEBSITE MAY NOT FUNCTION PROPERLY WITHOUT THE AID OF COOKIES.  IF YOU REFUSE COOKIES, YOU ASSUME ALL RESPONSIBILITY FOR ANY RESULTING LOSS OF FUNCTIONALITY.  
This Privacy Policy applies only to Personal Information gathered by means of the Website.  OhGizmo may supplement the Personal Information gathered by means of the Website with additional information gathered from public sources or from third-parties (e.g., consumer reporting agencies) that may lawfully provide such information to OhGizmo such supplemental information is not covered by this Privacy Policy.  Nor does this Privacy Policy apply to information provided by You to Third-Party Websites, which, as discussed above and below, may have data collection, storage and use practices and policies that differ materially from this Privacy Policy.  
YOU ARE UNDER NO OBLIGATION TO PROVIDE PERSONAL INFORMATION, WITH THE CAVEAT THAT YOUR REFUSAL TO DO SO MAY PREVENT YOU FROM USING CERTAIN FEATURES OF THE WEBSITE OR FROM MAKING PURCHASES OR RESERVATIONS BY MEANS OF THE WEBSITE.

4\.  INFORMATION USE AND DISCLOSURE PRACTICES  
(a)  Traffic Data and Information Gathered Using Cookies.  OhGizmo may analyze Traffic Data and information gathered using Cookies to help OhGizmo and OhGizmo’s licensors and suppliers better understand who is using the Website and how they are using it.  By identifying patterns and trends in usage, OhGizmo is able to better design the Website to improve Your experience, and to serve You more relevant and interesting content and advertisements.  From time to time, OhGizmo may release Traffic Data and information gathered using Cookies in the aggregate, such as by publishing a report on trends in the usage of the Website.  Other than by using cookies to store Your user name and password, OhGizmo does not attempt to link information gathered using Cookies to Personal Information.  
(b) Personal Information?(i)  Generally.  OhGizmo uses Your Contact Data to send You information about OhGizmo and OhGizmo’s goods and services, to contact You as necessary in connection with Your transactions with OhGizmo, and to send You other communications that You have agreed to receive.  OhGizmo uses Your Financial Data to verify Your qualifications for certain goods and/or services, and to charge You for Your for transactions with OhGizmo. OhGizmo uses Your Demographic Data to customize and tailor Your experience on the Website.  OhGizmo uses Your Transactional Data to fulfill its obligations in connection with Your transactions, and to provide customer service to You.  As with Traffic Data and information gathered using Cookies, from time to time OhGizmo may release Demographic Data in the aggregate, such as by publishing a report on trends in the usage of the Website.  
(ii)  Disclosure in Connection with Provision of Goods and Services.  OhGizmo may disclose Personal Information to those who help it provide the goods and services made available by means of the Website, including the suppliers of those goods and services and those who perform technical, administrative and data processing tasks such as hosting, billing, fulfillment, and data storage and security.  The third parties to whom OhGizmo discloses Personal Information all have agreed to abide by this Privacy Policy with respect to the information provided to them by OhGizmo (although, as discussed below, some of those third parties have separate privacy policies that govern their collection, use and storage of information that You provide to them directly).  
(iii)  Other Disclosure.  OhGizmo also discloses Personal Information under the following circumstances:  
By Law or to Protect Rights – OhGizmo discloses Personal Information when required to do so by law, or in response to a subpoena or court order, or when OhGizmo believes in its sole discretion that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of OhGizmo, third parties or the public at large.  
Marketing Communications – As stated in the Terms of Use, by using the Website, You consent to receive from OhGizmo periodic email communications regarding OhGizmo&amprsquos products and services.  OhGizmo may also provide Your Contact Information to third parties, so that they may contact You directly with information about additional products and services that OhGizmo believes may be of interest to You (”Marketing Communications”).  You may opt-out of having Your Contact Information provided to third parties for the purpose of Marketing Communications, by contacting OhGizmo at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)  For additional information, see the section concerning User Ability to Access, Update, and Correct Personal Information, below.  Even after opting-out, You may continue to receive Marketing Communications from third parties to whom OhGizmo already has provided Your Contact Information.  You will be responsible for contacting those third parties directly to request that You receive no further Marketing Communications.  You are under no obligation to receive Marketing Communications, with the caveat that Your refusal to do so may prevent You from making purchases or reservations by means of the Website.  OhGizmo will not itself, and will not provide mobile telephone Contact Information to others to, send Marketing Communications via mobile telephone text message.  
Business Transfers Bankruptcy – OhGizmo reserves the right to transfer all Personal Information in its possession to a successor organization in the event of a merger, acquisition, or bankruptcy or other sale of all or a portion of OhGizmo&amprsquos assets.  Other than to the extent ordered by a bankruptcy or other court, the use and disclosure of all transferred Personal Information will be subject to this Privacy Policy, or to a new privacy policy if You are given notice of that new privacy policy and an opportunity to affirmatively opt-out of it.  Personal Information submitted or collected after a transfer, however, may be subject to a new privacy policy adopted by OhGizmo&amprsquos successor organization.  
Unpaid Accounts – If You fail to pay any balance owed in consideration of any transaction with OhGizmo, OhGizmo may, as permitted by law, report Your Personal Information, including without limitation Your Financial Data and Transactional Data, to consumer credit reporting services, collection agencies and others.

5\. SECURITY OF PERSONAL INFORMATION  
OhGizmo has implemented and maintains reasonable security procedures and practices to protect against the unauthorized access, use, modification, destruction or disclosure of Your Personal Information.

6\. USER ABILITY TO ACCESS, UPDATE, AND CORRECT PERSONAL INFORMATION  
OhGizmo wants Your Personal Information to be complete and accurate.  As stated in the Website Terms of Use, by using the Website, You represent and warrant that all information You provide in connection with any Reservation, Application or otherwise in connection with Your use of the Website will be complete and accurate, and that You will update that information as necessary to maintain its completeness and accuracy.  To confirm the completeness and accuracy of, or make changes to, Your Personal Information, visit Your personal profile at OhGizmo.com.  Through Your personal profile You may review and update Your Personal Information that we have already collected.

7\.  THIRD-PARTY WEBSITES  
OhGizmo neither owns nor controls Third-Party Websites.  Accordingly, the operators of Third-Party Websites, including without limitation Vendors, are under no obligation to comply with this Privacy Policy except with respect to Personal Information provided directly to them by OhGizmo.  Before visiting or providing information to a Third-Party Website, You should inform Yourself of the privacy policies and practices (if any) of that Third-Party Website, and should take those steps necessary to, in Your discretion, protect Your privacy.  
The Site contains links to web sites of third parties. (Publisher) is not responsible for the actions of these third parties, including their privacy practices and any content posted on their web sites. We encourage you to review their privacy policies to learn more about what, why and how they collect and use personal information. (Publisher) adheres to industry recognized standards to secure any personal information in our possession, and to secure it from unauthorized access and tampering. However, as is true with all online actions, it is possible that third parties may unlawfully intercept transmissions of personal information, or other users of the Site may misuse or abuse your personal information that they may collect from the Site.  
(Publisher) uses third-party advertising companies to serve our ads on the Site. These third-party advertising companies employ cookie and 1×1 pixel .gifs or web beacons to measure and improve the effectiveness of ads for their clients. To do so, these companies may use anonymous information about your visits to our website and other websites, but will not collect any information which can personally identify you or can be linked to you. This information can include: date/time of banner ad shown, the banner ad that was shown, their cookie, and the IP address. This information can also be used for online preference marketing purposes.  
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads and collect information when users visit our site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements on our site, other websites and other forms of media about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, check out http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp.  
If you want to prevent a third-party advertiser from collecting data, currently you may either visit each ad network’s web site individually and opt out or visit the NAI gateway opt-out site to opt-out of all network advertising cookies. Click here for the NAI gateway opt-out site.?This site will also allow you to review the third-party advertising companies’ privacy policies.

8\.  PROMOTIONAL ACTIVITIES  
From time to time, OhGizmo may conduct contests, giveaways and other promotions (collectively, “Promotional Activities”).  Any information submitted in connection with Promotional Activities will be treated in accordance with this Privacy Policy.  From time to time, OhGizmo may also ask You to participate in surveys designed to help OhGizmo improve the Website.  Any Personal Information provided to OhGizmo in connection with any survey will be used only in relation to that survey and will be disclosed to third parties not bound by this Privacy Policy only in aggregated form.
